<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Washington Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="app_name_short">WTG</string>
    <string name="neutral_dialog_button">Close</string>

    <array name="place_names">
        <item>Juanitos Mexican Restaurant</item>
        <item>Allie\'s Cupcakery &amp; Café</item>
        <item>William\'s Irish Tavern</item>
        <item>Empanada Mamasita</item>
        <item>Washington Diner</item>
        <item>Dave\'s Friendly Services Inc</item>
        <item>Warren County Liquors LLC</item>
        <item>Castle Family Dentistry, LLC. Brian C. Bialiy, DMD</item>
        <item>M Y Accounting and Tax Services</item>
        <item>Albea Americas, Inc</item>
        <item>Faith Discovery Church</item>
        <item>United Methodist Church</item>
        <item>First Presbyterian Church</item>
        <item>St. Joseph Roman Catholic Church</item>
        <item>Worship Church Washington</item>
        <item>Roaring Rock Park</item>
        <item>Von Thun Farms</item>
        <item>Pohatcong Native Arboretum</item>
        <item>Washington Borough Pocket Park</item>
        <item>Taylor Street School</item>
        <item>Warren Hills Regional Middle School</item>
        <item>Brass Castle Elementary School</item>
        <item>Memorial Elementary School</item>
        <item>Warren Hills Regional High School</item>
    </array>

    <array name="place_addresses">
        <item>3 Broad St</item>
        <item>7 Broad St</item>
        <item>101 E Washington Ave</item>
        <item>65 E Washington Ave</item>
        <item>6 NJ-31</item>
        <item>288 W Washington Ave</item>
        <item>260 W Washington Ave</item>
        <item>151 W Washington Ave 1st floor</item>
        <item>111 W Washington Ave</item>
        <item>191 NJ-31</item>
        <item>33 Brass Castle Rd</item>
        <item>116 E Washington Ave</item>
        <item>40 E Church St</item>
        <item>200 Carlton Ave</item>
        <item>38 Kinnaman Ave</item>
        <item>Harmony Brass Castle Rd</item>
        <item>438 NJ-57</item>
        <item>52 Mine Hill Rd</item>
        <item>44 E Washington Ave</item>
        <item>16 Taylor St #24</item>
        <item>64-66 Carlton Ave</item>
        <item>16 Castle St</item>
        <item>300 W Stewart St</item>
        <item>41 Jackson Valley Rd</item>
    </array>

    <array name="place_descriptions">
        <item>The experienced chefs of Juanitos Mexican Restaurant in Washington create authentic
            Mexican Cuisine using fresh ingredients and traditional recipes.
        </item>
        <item>Allie\'s Cupcakery &amp; Café is an eatery years in the making. In fact, you might say
            that its origins date all the way back to 1949! That was the year Josephine Pistilli, my
            grandma, opened Pistilli\'s Family Restaurant in Bernardsville, NJ. She spent years
            cooking, expanding, and perfecting her business. Having lived a stone\'s throw away
            (literally) from her restaurant until my early twenties, I spent most of my time
            learning and working by my grandma\'s side.
        </item>
        <item>William’s Irish Tavern welcomes you like an old friend. Everyday we greet and serve
            our friends and neighbors in Washington, NJ just like our namesake did years ago.
            Colonel William McCullough opened the very first tavern in Washington Borough, New
            Jersey in 1811. Colonel McCullough built his tavern to build his community; through the
            sharing of food and drink many great ideas and great friendships were born. With
            numerous popular and craft beer choices and a menu full of traditional pub favorites, so
            on continues the tradition of great food, great drink and great friends at William’s
            Irish Tavern today. Cheers!
        </item>
        <item>Latin comfort food.</item>
        <item>The key to our success is simple: providing quality consistent food that taste great
            every single time. We pride ourselves on serving our customers delicious genuine dishes
            like: American.
        </item>
        <item>Welcome to Dave\'s Friendly Service! We are a full service, automotive repair and
            maintenance shop serving the Washington area since 1976. We understand that sometimes
            car repair can be stressful and we do everything possible to make our customers feel
            welcome, comfortable and satisfied with their service experience. We make your service
            experience hassle-free. We are happy to offer early bird and night-owl drop-box service
            and local shuttle service to your home or office.
        </item>
        <item>Fine liquor, wine, spirits, and beer.</item>
        <item>The true test of a quality dental office is the longevity of its staff. Castle Family
            Dentistry is proud that, on average, our staff has been with us for over 13 years. They
            provide a familiar, caring environment that you can trust.
        </item>
        <item>They do taxes and stuff. Idk.</item>
        <item>Big company with no website to get info from. Not sure what they do. Lol.</item>
        <item>Here at FDC we have three Core Values by which we strive to live. Authentic, be real!
            Accepting, be loving! Accelerating, be encouraging!
        </item>
        <item>Greenstone is a welcoming and affirming community of faith located in the heart of
            Downtown Washington, NJ. We are thrilled to provide you with a Christ centered
            experience and an environment to nurture your spirit or raise a family.
        </item>
        <item>Orange Presbyterian church.</item>
        <item>Welcome! And thank you for visiting our Parish web site. The pages of this site speak
            of a humble and proud family. Humble in our beginning and reality of who we are before
            God, and proud to be a people doing his work for over 140 years. As you scroll through
            these pages please keep us in your prayers as we will remember you.
        </item>
        <item>To know Jesus and experience Him is our greatest call. Our mission is to live and make
            disicples consecrated to Him. We do this through living in authenitc community and
            offering multiple ways to get involved, grow and stay connected.
        </item>
        <item>Hiking trail up by Brass Castle Road.</item>
        <item>Nestled in scenic Warren County, VonThun Farms is open spring, summer, and fall with
            events and activities for the whole family! Visit the New Jersey Sunflower Trail, New
            Jersey’s premier sunflower destination. Stop into our farm market for homegrown fruits,
            vegetables and angus beef and pick your own strawberries, raspberries, blackberries,
            peaches, apples and pumpkins.
        </item>
        <item>Pohatcong Native Arboretum, Native Tree Museum of New Jersey, has an exhibition on
            display of over 155 species of native trees, shrubs, and vines. The plants are
            identified by plaques with common, family, genus, and species names. Between 2010 and
            2015 our plant collection was tripled.
        </item>
        <item>Small park nestled between some businesses in the boro.</item>
        <item>Taylor Street Elementary School is a public school located in Washington, NJ, which is
            in a fringe town setting.The student population of Taylor Street Elementary School is
            188, and the school serves PK-2.
        </item>
        <item>Warren Hills Regional Middle School is comprised of 659 diverse 7th and 8th grade
            students. Our Middle School structure includes two departmentally clustered grade level
            teams. Presently, the range of academic opportunities for students includes courses in
            Language Arts Literacy, Mathematics, Science, Social Studies, World Languages, Visual
            &amp; Performing Arts, Fine Arts, Computer Applications, Health &amp; Physical
            Education, Music, Careers, Computer Assisted Instruction for Math and Language Arts and
            Interdisciplinary Enrichment. All areas of study benefit from the expansion of our
            technological resources through our district technology plan. Teachers have access to a
            variety of technological tools, which are used to enhance and supplement educational
            pedagogy.
        </item>
        <item>Our school district consists of two elementary schools, the Port Colden School and the
            Brass Castle School, educating students in grades kindergarten through sixth. Washington
            Township School District is a place that reflects, nurtures and promotes the sense of
            fellowship so valued by the community it serves.
        </item>
        <item>Washington Memorial Elementary School is a public school located in WASHINGTON, NJ. It
            has 268 students in grades 3-6 with a student-teacher ratio of 11 to 1. According to
            state test scores, 40% of students are at least proficient in math and 52% in reading.
        </item>
        <item>Warren Hills Regional High School is a four-year public high school located on Jackson
            Valley Road in Washington Township in Warren County, New Jersey, United States,
            operating as part of the Warren Hills Regional School District.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="place_categories">
        <item>Restaurants</item>
        <item>Businesses</item>
        <item>Religion</item>
        <item>Fun</item>
        <item>Schools</item>
    </array>

</resources>